I've made over $1 million in just the
last year trading crypto meme coins. But
if I lost it all today, in this video,
I'm going to show you exactly how I do
it all over again to make my first 100K,
even if you have zero knowledge. I know
you clicked on this video for a reason.
You've seen people making life-changing
money, 100x, 500x returns in days,
sometimes hours, while you're
continuously losing trades, not knowing
what to do. My goal with this free
course is to make it better than all the
other gurus out there who are forcing
you to pay. I'm 19, handsome, a
millionaire, and I left Cornell to do
this full-time, and I'm 66. Okay, maybe
not that last part, but I am about to
break it all down for you from the exact
setup, filters, live strategies, and
principles I use myself till this day.
If you really want to get results, stay
locked in because I'm about to reveal
some priceless knowledge. Let's get into
it. So, before you even think about
trades, what is the right setup? What
tools should you be using? What apps?
Where do you need to stay active? So, in
step number one, I'm going to break down
everything my friends and I use to make
millions from our PCs. So, first things
first, I highly recommend you trade on a
PC or a laptop instead of your phone.
Trading on a PC or a laptop offers you a
larger screen, better functionality, you
can move between tabs a lot more easily,
and the tools you need to trade with are
going to be a lot more easy to use. In
meme coins, a split second can be the
difference between making hundreds of
thousands or remaining sidelined. Speed
and visibility are essential. If you're
trading on a PC, get more monitors. It's
going to make your life a lot easier. I
promise. For reference, here's my setup.
The next thing you need is a Twitter or
X account. Crypto Twitter is the most
important platform for research. And if
you go through my videos on my wins,
you'll see that all of them involve
doing research on Twitter before buying
in. Now, if you want to get your Twitter
account crypto ready, follow as many
accounts as you can on the screen that
I'm about to show you. You essentially
want to change your for you page from
the regular stuff that Twitter is
showing you into crypto news,
cryptoreated content. Next, what you're
going to need is a Telegram or Discord
account. Community is one of the most
important parts of a coin, and Telegram
and Discord are going to be your main
communication platforms for memecoins.
Then, what you'll need is Salana, the
biggest crypto used for memecoins. This
is where communities around memecoins
form, and developers or insiders are
going to be dropping important
information and announcements in here.
Then what you'll need is Salana, the
biggest crypto used for memecoins. Now,
how do I buy Salana? Step one, set up a
Salana wallet. So, you need to create a
digital cold wallet compatible with the
Salana blockchain. And the best one at
the moment is Phantom wallet. Just go to
phantom.com, hit download for Chrome if
that's what you're using, add to Chrome,
add extension, and then you're going to
create a new wallet right here. Create a
seed phrase wallet. Set up a password
that you like. And once you get to this
step, it's going to give you a bunch of
words as you can see on the screen here.
Make sure you save this offline. Write
it down on a piece of paper if you have
to. If anything happens and you lose
your wallet, this is the only way to
recover it and you don't want anyone
besides yourself to know this phrase.
But once you're done, hit I have saved
my recovery phrase. Continue and then
give yourself a username. I'll just make
it Alex Crypto Tutorial and you should
be good. You've got the Phantom
extension right here. Once you've got
the Salana wallet set up, you need a
purchase sold through a cryptocurrency
exchange. You can use Coinbase, Binance,
Kraken, whatever works for your region.
For my example, I'll be using Coinbase.
So, go to your Phantom, go to the Salana
wallet address you've got here, copy it,
click send crypto, paste it in, and you
should be good to send however much soul
you purchased. Next, you're going to
need a good trading bot to buy and sell
meme coins with your soul as fast as
possible. The best one in the space
right now is Axiom. It has the fastest
fills, the most features, and the
cheapest gas fees. So, to set this up,
go to the sign up button right here, and
you can sign up either with a Gmail or
your Phantom wallet that we just set up.
But whatever you use, make sure to put
down fortune as the invite code right
here down below. I've gotten a
partnership with them just to give you
guys the lowest fees out of any other
Axiom user out there. Now that you're
in, first thing you're going to do,
click the button at the top right right
here. Head to account and security.
Click view recovery key. Confirm. Same
exact thing with your Phantom wallet.
This is going to give you a seed phrase
that you should save externally. It's
the only way you'll be able to recover
your Axiom wallet address if anything
happens to it. Once you've got that set
up, head to the poll section right here.
And this is where every new meme coin
that comes out is going to be shown. And
it's where you're going to be watching
99% of the time for plays. First thing
you're going to do here is change the
filters. So head to new pairs right here
on the left. Click the little button
here. And the first thing you need to
make sure is that Pump Fund is the only
protocol selected. Radium and Moonshot
coins are pretty low volume. They're not
going to perform that well. Pump Fund is
where all the volume is going to be.
Then you're going to go down, go to the
middle, click on metrics, and for the
market cap right here, put in minimum
13,000. This cleans out all the garbage
that won't perform, and it's going to
give you early enough entry on the ones
that do have potential. And that's all
you'll need. You can filter out coins
with snipers or insiders, but there are
times where coins with both do run
extremely high due to having a good
enough narrative. So, I personally just
leave it like this. Then, you're going
to change your buy and sell presets to
make sure that you get the most
efficient fills. So to do this, click on
the presets button right here next to
your active wallets. First thing you're
going to do is change your slippage to
30%. With how much price can fluctuate
for meme coins, your slippage needs to
be this high in order for your buys to
fill. Any higher or lower, and you could
risk not getting filled or buying at too
high of an entry. Price fluctuates a ton
for meme coins. Your slippage needs to
be this high in order for your buys to
fill. Next, your priority and your
bribery fee. So, these depend a little
more on how much capital you have, but I
would personally set it to something
like 0.03 for both. This ensures that
your fills beat the competition if
you're trying to snipe a coin early. And
then finally, you're going to turn me
protection on. Without this, your buys
are going to get front ran and
sandwiched by bots, and it's going to
absolutely kill your entry. Now, you're
going to do the same exact thing with
your cell presets, but leave slippage at
40 and change the priority and bribery
to 0.03 each. Mer protection on, and you
should be good. Next, for your quick
buy, you're going to change this to
whatever amount you're comfortable
buying these new low cap meme coins with
relative to your portfolio size. So,
this is going to be the amount of soul
for your first buy for the meme coins
that you're looking at over here. So,
for me, I tend to keep this around 5 to
10 soul, but with a smaller port, you
might want to change it to something
like one. And a little trick I'm about
to show you, do
0.0000. And now your buttons for the
quick buy is going to be a lot bigger.
It's going to be a lot more easy to buy
into this stuff. These are the absolute
highest risk plays. Finally, you're
going to add Salana to your Axiom wallet
by selecting the little wallet button
right here. Click deposit. Now you've
got your Axiom wallet address right
here. Copy it. Head to Phantom. Go to
Soul. Make sure you copy and paste the
Axiom wallet address into the recipient
Solana address right here on Phantom.
And then whatever amount of Soul you're
comfortable with putting in. Now your
Axiom's all set up. Once your setup is
done, now you're ready to actually hop
in the trenches and start making some
trades. But you yourself know that the
game of crypto and meme coins is
ruthless and it's even worse when you're
trading solo because you're likely to
get farmed. So in step number two,
here's my advice on how to speed up your
learning curve. But before that, let me
tell you a story that'll help you
understand why. So back when I first
started trading meme coins, I would see
these free Telegram groups on Twitter
all the time. They'd have one person
running them and they'd have hyped
announcements where they'd say they'd
drop a play at a certain time, but the
entire time it was literally just them
launching their own coins, picking up
most of the supply and then selling on
their own community on the call. These
were also locked chats where I couldn't
talk, learn, network. So, all I gained
by being there was a red number.
Remember guys, there's no such thing as
free alpha. Please do not fall for these
kind of things. There's always a price
on everything in life. You can apply to
trade with me personally in the link in
the description below. I'm working with
people like Co and Cood in the crypto
Twitter community who have made millions
in their public wallets and are now
calling bangers in my group fortune.
We've been hitting absolute cooks
recently, even in this market where we
front ran a Coinbase listing, the
highest volume crypto exchange on dog
and me and another listing from an
exchange on Keycat. From buying before
huge insiders to trenching daily, we've
made millions trading as a crypto
community. Even people who were
completely new to crypto only a month
ago are now making their own calls and
profiting off not just ours, but their
own. But it doesn't just have to be with
me. There's a bunch of other groups,
people out there on crypto Twitter that
have good track records. And trading
with them is not only going to help you
progress immensely, but also expose
yourself to a good network. The biggest
connections I made have all originally
come from crypto. Even just trading with
your friends is going to give you an
advantage. Just don't be leveling solo.
You now have the proper setup. You know
how to find a community. But how do you
dominate on the actual charts? Not all
meme coins are created equal. And
probably the biggest issue people have
is doing proper research and knowing how
to value these coins to see if they'll
blow up or not. So in step number three,
I'll show you how to find your own 100x.
And this is the same system I use to
make 200K in one crypto trade. So the
first and most important metric you're
going to use is narrative. Now narrative
is a really broad concept when it comes
to crypto, but it's the most important
thing to understand when it comes to
valuing a coin. Ask yourself these
questions. So number one is what is the
story behind the coin and what makes it
valuable? Ask yourself what is the meme
or trend that the coin is about? Maybe
it's a coin about Elon tweeting or maybe
Trump said something really memeable.
You want to find out what is the coin
based around. And then you need to
figure out why this story is valuable.
For example, why would the story of
Trump making a memecoin be valuable?
Because it's the most popular man in the
world making a memecoin. That is
something that's going to get attention.
And in crypto, attention equals value.
something like the most popular man in
the world launching his own memecoin is
going to generate a lot of attention.
So, there's a lot of value behind that
and it's why my group was able to make a
combined 8 million off this play. So,
when I'm talking about a story, is the
coin part of a movement? Does it solve a
problem or is it speculation? So, Trump,
for example, would be speculation of him
launching a memecoin and being a part of
a movement, Trump finally joining
memecoin culture. And when you look at
these stories, you need to be thinking
of future bull catalysts. Always ask
yourself if the coin is at $10 million
market cap for example, why would
someone buy it at a hundred million?
What are future points that'll sustain
or grow the story? A good example of a
coin that solves a problem would be
something like ARC over here which went
645 million market cap. So let me tell
you a little tip on how to value these
utility coins, these problem-solving
coins. So something like ARC is a
framework for developing AI
applications. Sounds complicated, right?
But remember, what's something I can
instantly look at for a coin like this
and know it's going to get attention. If
I open the website for ARC, I scroll
down, I can see ecosystem partners right
here, Salana, Arbitrum, and Abstract.
Huge multi-million billion dollar
partners. And having partners those huge
connected to the coin is going to draw
attention and therefore makes the coin's
narrative valuable. So it doesn't matter
how complex whatever you're looking at
is, you just want to look at it from a
normal person's perspective and try to
figure out why is this story going to
get attention? And with narratives, you
always need to be looking for future
bull catalysts. So this means, for
example, if the coin is at $10 million
market cap, why would someone buy this
at 100 mil? So this could be through
ongoing development if it's a coin that
solves a problem. It could be a
potential listing on an exchange if the
coin is big enough, or there could be
more hype or upcoming updates or events
around the story. So, for example, an AI
coin that's continuously building could
have a better long-term narrative than a
news-based memecoin that had one big
moment and then would sell the news
after. So, for baseline, a stronger and
more compelling story is going to get
more attention and that's going to lead
to a higher value narrative. Now that
you know what a coin's narrative is, the
next question you need to answer is how
does this coin's narrative compare to
other coins? And to answer this, you
need to know what is a meta and the meta
is the current leading narrative. So,
every time you buy a coin, you need to
ask yourself, how does the narrative of
the coin fit into the current meta? For
example, if we're in an AI meta, AI
coins are generally going to get more
attention. But just because this is an
AI meta doesn't mean non AI coins 100%
won't perform well. So, if you find
yourself buying an offmeta coin, think
about why it might have the strength and
uniqueness to differentiate itself and
outperform among all the other oneta AI
coins. So, off-meta plays can still
work. A pretty extreme example of this
would be Trump. It dropped in a time
where AI Meta was going crazy. And even
though it wasn't an AI coin, the
narrative of this coin was so strong
that it didn't matter that it wasn't an
AI coin. So off meta plays can still
work, but they need to be unique or have
some kind of strength to stand out among
other trending plays. And in every meta,
there's something called alpha plays and
beta plays. The alpha plays, a little
corny, I know, but stay with me. So the
alpha plays are the highest market cap
coins with the most mind share and the
beta plays are smaller copycat coins.
Think of them as coke plays. So when dog
with hatcoin went parabolic, the dog
memecoin narrative gained a lot of
strength. So for a while we were in a
dog or a whiff meta. So in this example,
whiff is the alpha play. And during this
time in early November when whiff almost
went to 5 billion market cap, whiff had
other beta plays running as well. And
the beta plays would be the dog coins
that pumped because of the dog or whiff
meta that was happening. So for example,
dog with nunchucks at around early mid
November when whiff was running it up,
dog with nunchucks went from 2.5 million
to almost 25 million market cap and
catwift bagcoin right here which was the
whiff dog's real sister performed
extremely well in the same time frame.
You can see this massive candle in early
mid November. So some of the beta plays
of whiff would be ninja and bag. The
thing with beta plays though is that
they're not guaranteed to go up just
because the alpha is performing. A lot
of the times beta plays actually die and
never recover even if the alpha keeps up
its strength. So it's extremely
important to manage risk with these. If
I compare with the alpha with back the
beta. Yeah, I know it sounds stupid, but
you can see that when the market pulls
back right here, the beta play is much
weaker than the alpha. In any case
though, strong beta plays can reach up
to 10% of the alpha plays market cap.
So, it's definitely not a bad strategy
to play them if you can get a good entry
for a beta for a high market cap coin.
Just be sure to not get distracted by
too many derivatives. Usually, only one
or two betas will actually be strong
plays. So, you know what the coin story
is and how to value it, and you know how
relevant the story is right now. The
final question you need to answer about
a coin's narrative is where can I find
the narrative and how do I research it?
Your main tool for this is going to be
Axiom. I'm going to check the coin's
Twitter, website, Telegram, and search
it up on Twitter manually. And off those
things I mentioned, you're going to look
for three answers. So, what type of coin
is it? Is it a problem-solving utility
coin? Is it a news coin? Is it a
problem-solving utility based coin? Is
it a political news-based coin? You need
to know what type of coin it is to
understand its story. Next, who is
following or supporting the project.
Sometimes the people supporting the
project alone can be a narrative. So,
for example, if a rich and powerful VC
is following the coin's Twitter, that's
a narrative that's going to get huge
attention. And then finally, what is the
coin about? What's the trend, meme,
news, tech that the coin is covering?
And you can find the answer to these
through Axium. On the Twitter page, look
through the followers and following
list. Look through the posts, if there's
a GitHub, if it's a utility
problem-solving coin. Look for
announcements in the Telegram. Look at
what other people are saying about the
coin on Twitter through manual search.
And you should be able to find this
information in seconds once you get more
experience. So, you've got the coin's
narrative. Now, the next piece of
valuation that you need is the coin's
community. A coin can't get attention
without a community supporting it.
That's building hype, buying supply, and
bringing my share. So, the only question
you need to answer is how strong is the
community? And you can find this by
looking through the coin's Twitter,
Telegram, and Discord. And you're going
to be looking at how active the coin's
community is in these apps. How often is
the team pushing out announcements? How
many of the holders are actually
interacting? And especially on Twitter,
you want to find out how many
influential people on crypto Twitter are
following the account. So a coin like
this, Collaterize is a really good
example. They're consistently updating
and building. They've got a lot of
influential people following the account
and they're getting more and more
funding from collaborations. This is an
example of a strong community. And
another point you want to focus on,
especially on some older coins, is how
old is the community? If the coin and
community have been around for a while
and they've survived a lot of price draw
downs and they've still been active for
those periods of low activity, that's
going to be a really good sign of
strength. So, what you're pretty much
looking for is a cult. You want a cult
backing you up. Think of early Pepe,
Dogwift Hat, Shea Enu. And I'm not
saying the next meme coin you buy is
going to be like one of those, but you
want to look for an audience that's
going to follow the coin no matter the
conditions. So, we've got the coin
story, the people backing it up, and now
the final thing we need to look at is
the coin's numbers. So, for us to value
the stats, we need to look at the coin's
price action. So, price action is the
raw data of how the coin is moving on
the chart. And price action is usually
what gets you interested in the coin at
the start. If you look through my live
trading video, you're going to see that
on every single coin I bought, the first
thing that caught my eye was the volume
that every single coin was getting. So,
for example, you're sitting on Axiom and
you see a coin getting volume by seeing
how quickly the market cap is changing.
It's in your best interest. The second
you see that volume, that's a sign for
you to do research. So that means go to
the coin's Twitter, look it up on
Twitter manually, and just do some quick
research for a couple seconds. So let me
use this coin dog and me as an example.
A coin we front ran at my group fortune,
which we bought before insiders listed
it on Coinbase right here. When I look
at this chart, I want to ask myself this
question. And this is going to apply to
new pairs on Axiom, too. Has the coin
been performing very well recently? And
is it up by multiples? And if it is,
usually, unless it's an extremely strong
narrative, it's probably best to wait
for a good dip before you buy. Pretty
much every meme coin, even big ones like
Doge and Pepe, experience multiple 50 to
80% draw downs. And Coinbase insiders
probably have most of the supply in this
coin after the listing. So, I'd be a
little careful about buying at the top
here. So, for new pairs, you really want
to focus on volume, while for old coins,
you're looking for strength. And to find
strength during these draw downs, you
want to assess the community. Look
through the coins Twitter and find out
if they still believe in the narrative.
Patience is so important when it comes
to investments, not only after you buy,
but before as well. Now, we've got the
three metrics on how to value a coin.
But the final thing we need to take note
of is the coin's legitimacy. Seems a
little obvious, but does the coin seem
scammy? And Axium is going to be a
lifesaver when you're figuring this out.
If you look at the little symbols over
here, Axium is going to show you almost
all the information you need to know if
the coin's legit. So, the first symbol
my mouse is hovering over, that's going
to be how much of the supply is being
held by the top 10 holders. The bigger
this number is, the bigger of a red
flag. Next one, the little chef symbol,
if it says DS, that means the dev sold.
If there's a percentage, that's going to
be how much of the dev is holding. The
bigger this number is, the more of a red
flag. But if it's a problem-solving
utility-based coin and it says dev sold
because a techcoin needs the developer
supporting the project. Next one is
snipers. This is going to show how much
of the supply is being held by people
who bought in the first block. So on the
first transaction, any snipers at all is
usually a bad sign. It's almost always
the dev buying in on separate wallets
through a bot. Next, you've got the
little go symbol right here. and that's
going to be how much supply the insiders
of the coin are holding. And insider
wallets are wallets that have been sent
supply from the dev wallet. Insiders are
okay if the narrative supports it. Now,
what do I mean by this? So, let's say
Elon reveals his public wallet right
here. And someone decides to make an
Elon coin. And when they do, they send
Elon 80% of the coin supply. Now, in
this case, Elon's wallet would show up
as an insider with 80% of the supply.
You have a guy with some of the most
influence in crypto holding 80% of your
coin. That's going to help the
narrative. But outside of those
scenarios where insiders are part of the
narrative, a coin with high insiders is
usually something you want to avoid. And
now the last thing is the bundle. So the
bundle is the percent supply that the
developer is putting into hidden side
wallets. But almost every coin is going
to have some kind of bundle. So the
stronger the narrative is, the less the
bundle starts to matter. And another
cool thing Axiom does is if you hover
over the Twitter logo, it shows you how
many times the Twitter's name was
changed. So for example, this coin right
here, Duterte, it shows that the
Twitter's had multiple names before. And
that usually means that the coin's
Twitter was involved in a project before
and you're going to want to avoid that
most of the time. And of course, you're
also going to want to check for typos on
the coin socials and websites and search
the coin name to see if it's done before
or if it's a copy. If you take all these
measures for legitimacy, it's going to
be a lot harder for you to get scammed.
Now, you know how to value these coins.
But when we look at the data, 70 to 75%
of people lose money in their first year
of trading. The other 20 to 25% lose
money in the next 5 years. And only 3 to
5% of traders are profitable or not
losing money. And it all comes down to
step number four, risk management, which
is where the majority of people, maybe
like you, end up burning their
hard-earned money. Making money is so
easy in this space. But keeping it is
the difficult part. So here's the risk
management system I implemented after I
lost all my money and almost went broke
last summer. I actually roundt the first
six figures I made trading meme points.
Not because I didn't know how to find
good plays. I did. I was calling bangers
left and right. But my risk management
was awful. I was buying too much into
high-risisk plays, fomoing into top
charts just because everyone else was
talking about them. And soon enough, I
watched my entire portfolio evaporate. I
went from feeling unstoppable with six
figures at 18 to being completely wiped
out. That experience humbled me. But it
also forced me to build a real system, a
way to protect my capital and manage my
emotions. And it was only after I
experienced that loss that I was able to
make my first million. So here's exactly
how I managed my risk. so you don't have
to learn the hard way like I did. The
first thing you need to put in your head
is to one, never invest an amount of
money that you cannot afford to lose.
And two, never invest an amount of money
that you're not willing to lose. Now,
these sound really similar, but they're
actually two completely different
things. So, the first one's pretty easy
to understand. You just should never
trade with an amount that can negatively
affect your life. You always want to
consider whatever amount you're buying
with to be zero. If whatever trades
you're in instantly hit the gutter, that
should not affect your life in any sort
of way. pretty easy to understand. You
just want to be financially responsible.
But for number two, what I mean by not
willing to lose is that you need to be
comfortable in every single trade you're
in. And this is because you're not going
to capitulate trades as easily if you're
not emotionally affected by the amount
of money you invested with. Speaking of
capitulations, there are two types of
capitulations in crypto. Price-based
capitulation and timebased capitulation.
And knowing what these mean is going to
help you understand those principles a
lot easier. losses add up and trading
can be a bit scary when it comes to this
because at the end of the day it really
is just numbers on a screen. In price
based capitulation, a trader sells
because the price of the coin goes so
low to the point where it influences
them to no longer believe in the
narrative or their position goes through
so much of a draw down that they just
cut losses. And again, if you only
invest an amount you can afford and
you're willing to lose, it is extremely
hard to undergo price-based
capitulation. And this is because you
don't have to cut losses if the price
goes down. And even if your investment
goes to zero, it's not going to hurt you
because the amount is insignificant to
your portfolio. And in memecoin trading,
this is huge because so many times we
see coins go to zero, revive, and then
pull crazy multiples. With that being
said, you need to take this advice on a
tradeby-trade basis. And there are
definitely times when cutting losses is
the best decision, like if the project
actually rugs or if there's genuinely
bad news about the coin. The second type
of capitulation is timebased
capitulation. And in timebased
capitulation, the trader sells because
they simply get impatient regarding the
price action. Now, I'm not saying the
random coin you're holding in your
wallet is going to be the next Dogecoin.
But just think about how many people got
shaken out during those boring periods
of price action. So, there are two key
takeaways from this, and that's one,
always have a thesis and a plan whenever
you make a trade. Let's say I have a
large chunk of my board sized into Pepe.
Before I press buy, I need to know what
I'm getting myself into, the potential
draw down I'd have to hold through, and
how much money I'm willing to put into
the trade. Number two, never put too
much of your liquidity into one play.
This is going to mess with you
emotionally. You're going to sell out of
impatience or from seeing another coin
outperforming your current play. And for
that reason, you should always have
enough liquidity available to buy the
next play, even if you're holding
another coin. For example, even if a lot
of my money is put into a big coin like
Pepe, I still have enough liquidity to
size into another coin if I need to. One
little strategy I have to help with this
is to literally move your profits into a
different wallet. So, I trench with
about 50 soul in my wallet usually. And
whenever my wallet goes over this 50
from hitting a good trade, I just move
that money out. So, let's say this is my
wallet with 50 soul and it goes to 100
soul after I make 50 soul on a trade.
I'm simply going to make a new wallet
and then take 50 soul out of that
trading wallet into my new wallet. And
anytime my trading wallet goes over 50
soul, I'm going to keep adding over to
that new wallet that I made. And it's
going to act as a treasury for my money.
This way, I'm physically limiting my
risk and making it a habit to not have
to redeposit money back into my wallet.
Cuz for me, this 50 soul is all I need
to make money. And of course, you can
adjust that amount to your port. You
just need to remember we're in a bull
market and opportunities are going to
come daily. And that's both a blessing
and a curse. You need to stay grounded,
stick to your thesis, invest
responsibly, and do not chase green
candles. Do this and you will outperform
90% of market participants. And now Co's
at the point where he's making calls for
everybody else. Like the scan on this
coin right here, Pig Balls, at 1.9
million market cap. We've got his thesis
right here. And literally 2 hours later,
the coin went to 70 mil on our call
channel. And if you think this video is
full of great value, just imagine what
my circle is getting. For example, Co,
who I made a video on, went from
papering trades and not knowing how to
build conviction to making $3 million on
his public wallet after working and
trading with us personally. And
countless amount of others like you see
on the screen right now have done the
same. So, if you want to join in on the
success, click the first link down below
to apply. Now, we're on step five. Yeah,
it's hard to do research and understand
the value behind these coins, but the
hardest part of this entire crypto thing
is actually entering and exiting these
trades. That's what differentiates me, a
19-year-old millionaire, from some
random that enters a trade with a few
hundred and then watches it go to zero.
It's not that I'm smarter or any
different. You can do the same. I just
understand the concepts I was explaining
in the previous steps and this exit
strategy. So, you're sitting on Axiom,
you're seeing all these coins and using
the concepts that I taught you, you
finally find a good coin to buy into and
you're up a solid amount of money. How
do you exit? So, the most important
concept to understand is averaging. And
that's cuz price in memecoins is
extremely volatile. Things can change in
an instant from a person with influence
suddenly supporting the coin to a coin
with a stronger narrative coming out at
the same time and vamping yours and
overshadowing yours. And because of
this, it's almost impossible to time the
top or bottom of any coin. And that's
where averaging comes in. You should
never be selling your position in one
clip. Instead, what you're going to do
is average in on some trades, but always
average out. And that means you're going
to buy less than you intend to in case
you get a better entry. So, if you're
not too confident of where you're buying
at, buy 50% at one point and then 50% in
another. And that way, you can get more
size into a play and hopefully get
better entry. But, you're going to
always sell your position in 10 to 25%
clips whenever you're up enough money or
a bull catalyst is triggered. And a bull
catalyst can be something like an
influential person buying in, which is
going to lead to a lot of copy traders
or someone with a lot of pull tweets
about it. Elon for example. This way,
you're able to secure your initials and
some profits, but you still have some
stake left in the coin. the case that it
does go higher or if it rugs out of
nowhere, you still walk away with money.
If you see my $15,000 win here, you can
see that there's like a million
transactions on the screen. And I
actually have a live recording of that
trade right here. It's a trade I
executed very well. And I'm about to
walk you guys through the execution with
this trade as a demonstration. So, I saw
this coin because of the volume that it
was getting because price action is the
first indicator that the coin is getting
eyes. And I found out that the coin's
Twitter handle cost it $30,000. And I
knew that was something that was going
to get attention. And I saw that the
coin implemented technology during a
time where AI coins were doing really
well, meaning that we were in an AI
meta. So I decided to buy 10 soul. And
once I got my position, I did more
research on the coin and stayed updated
with any news that was coming out about
it. And surprisingly, the coin went down
70%. But because I implemented proper
risk management by only putting in an
amount I could afford to completely lose
and hold through draw downs with, I was
able to keep my emotions in check and
still believe in the thesis that this
coin was going to get attention with all
the catalysts that it had behind it. So
what do I do? I average more. And now I
have a better entry with more size. And
after that, I keep doing research on the
coin. I keep staying updated. And the
coin finally bounces. And I take my
initials here to be safe. And as the
trade goes on, partnerships started
lighting up for this coin. influential
people started buying in. My thesis
played out completely. And as you can
see, there's so many sells on the screen
because it's impossible to time the top
on a coin like this. So, I just sold bit
by bit to make my exit point as close to
the top as possible. And as you can see,
by the end of that trade, I made 45.6
sold. But at the end of the day, none of
this matters if you can't implement that
number six. A lot of people don't do
this, which is why most traders fail.
But me on the other hand, doing this is
exactly why I've lost tens of thousands
of dollars on trades, but then went on
to make hundreds of thousands of dollars
in trades. And that's because I actually
care about journaling. But Alex, how
should I journal? What should I even
focus on? I got you. So, after every
trade, write down and ask yourself these
four questions. One, what was the
narrative of the coin I bought? Two, why
did I buy where I did? Three, why did I
hold for how long I did? And four, why
did I sell where I did? Once you've
answered these, analyze and reflect on
what you could have done better for each
question. Nobody's a perfect trader.
Even I have instances where I look back
and I realize I could have executed this
a lot better. And also ask yourself what
you did well in these four questions and
how you can implement that into future
trades moving forward. And by doing
this, you always know where you are as a
trader in terms of your skill. You know
your trading style and if it's working
for the current meta the market's in. It
keeps you grounded and helps you look at
things from a more objective view. and
it always gives yourself room for
improvement. You need to understand that
memecoin trading isn't just about
winning one trade. You got to one accept
that losses happen. Detach yourself from
the outcome. Two, always refine your
strategy. The meta is always changing.
The trading style that worked during one
market condition might not work during
the other. And three, you got to think
long term. The real money in this game
is going to come from compounding
experience and the connections that you
make. Now you know exactly how to
conquer the market and eventually hit
trades like mine. But free education
alone isn't enough, which is why I
highly recommend you join Fortune, where
we are changing lives daily with the
first link down below. And if you want
to see a live breakdown of a $200,000
trade, check out this next video where I
explain exactly how I executed it.
Thanks for watching and peace.